A Guide to the Population Council records, International Programs, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 13 FA1433
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Programs, 1963-1986; 13
  - Routine Administration and Lippes Loops Files, 3
    - Inserters - Internal Reports, 1963-1967 (Box 31, Folder 248)
    - Inserters - Handbooks - Specs (Box 31, Folder 249)
    - Loops and Inserters - Use Problems, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 250)
    - IUDs - Dr. Rice-Wray, 1972-1975 (Box 31, Folder 251)
    - Contraceptives - Manufacturing - Bronnenkant - Hallmark Plastics, 1972-1975 (Box 31, Folder 252)
    - Contraceptives - Manufacturing - Ortho Pharmaceutical, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 253)
    - Contraceptives - Manufacturing - Sytex Lab, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 254)
    - Lippes Loops and Inserters - Manufacturers Drawings, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 255)
    - IUDs - "Caution" Inserts (Box 32, Folder 256)
    - Lippes Loops - Presterilized Packages, 1967-1976 (Box 32, Folder 257)
    - Ortho Pharmaceutical, 1968-1976 (Box 32, Folder 258)
    - Purchase of Lippes Loops by International Planned Parenthood Federation (IPPF), 1976 (Box 32, Folder 259)
    - Lippes Loops, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 260)
    - Population Roundtable Meetings, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 261)
    - Fleischmann Foundation, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 262)
    - Toward A Consistent Fiction (Box 33, Folder 263)
    - 1977 Budget and Funding - General Information, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 264)
    - 1978 Budget and Funding, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 265)
    - 1978 TAD Budget - Preparation and Backup, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 266)
    - Material for Future Activities Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 267)
    - Council Descriptions, 1976-1978 (Box 33, Folder 268)
    - International Programs - Descriptions, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 269)
    - International Programs - Staff Descriptions, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 270)
    - Betty McInnes - Principal Secretary Files, 1974-1977 (Box 33, Folder 271)
    - Maternal and Child Health - Family PlanningDemonstration Programs - Reviews, 1972-1978 (Box 33, Folder 272)
    - International Committee on Applied Research in Population (ICARP) - Reports and Reviews, 1974-1978 (Box 33, Folder 273)
    - International Postpartum Program, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 274)
    - Institutional Development, 1973-1978 (Box 34, Folder 275)
    - TAD Programs - Commercial Distribution Private Sector, 1970-1972 (Box 34, Folder 276)
    - TAD-IP - Summary of Information and Education Activities, 1972-1974 (Box 34, Folder 277)
    - International Programs - Signature Authorizations, 1975-1978 (Box 34, Folder 278)
    - Population Council Organizational Information, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 278A)
    - Population Council Policy Memos, 1971-1976 (Box 34, Folder 279)
    - Population Council Board of Trustees - Presidential Search, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 280)
    - CPS - Miscellaneous, 1972-1978 (Box 34, Folder 281)
    - Biomedical Division - International Committee for Contraception Research (ICCR) Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 282)
    - Comprollers Office - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 283)
    - Public Information Office (PIO) - General, 1971-1978 (Box 34, Folder 284)
    - Library Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 34, Folder 285)
    - Population Council Fellowship Program - General Information, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 286)
    - Personnel - Staff Directories (Box 34, Folder 287)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Personnel
    - Finland - Scientific Conference on Family and Population, 1984 May 25-27 (Box 35, Folder 288)
    - Ford Foundation, 1974-1985 (Box 35, Folder 289)
    - International Programs, 1976-1981 (Box 35, Folder 290)
    - International Programs-CPS Relations, 1979-1985 (Box 35, Folder 291)
    - Landauer Associates, Inc., 1980 (Box 35, Folder 292)
    - Population Council Library, 1977-1985 (Box 35, Folder 293)
    - LHRH Conference, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 294)
    - Population Council and Clubs that Discriminate Against Women, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 295)
    - International Programs Staff Appointments and Correspondence, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 296)
    - Donor Files - General, 1975-1977 (Box 36, Folder 297)
    - Donor Files International Committee on Applied Research in Population (ICARP), 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 298)
    - Donor Files - Ford Foundation, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 299)
    - Donor Files - General Services Foundation (GSF), 1970s (Box 36, Folder 300)
    - Donor Files - UNFPA, 1976-1978 (Box 36, Folder 301)
    - Donor Files - Government of Indonesia Projects, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 302)
    - Donor Files - AID, 1976-1978 (Box 37, Folder 303)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 304)
    - Affiliated Agencies, 1972-1978 (Box 37, Folder 305)
    - The International Committee on the Management of Population Programmes (ICOMP) (Box 37, Folder 306)
    - Preterm Institute, Inc., 1977 (Box 37, Folder 307)
    - AID - General - Funding, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 308)
    - Other Organizations - General, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 309)
    - East-West Center, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 310)
    - Durafoam - General, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 311)
    - Copper-T - General, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 312)
    - World Population Year, Bucharest, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 313)
    - Special Reports - Meeting on Commercial Sector, 1973 April 5 (Box 37, Folder 314)
    - Special Reports - Demographic Division Program Brief, 1975 November (Box 37, Folder 315)
    - Special Reports - Technical Assistance Division (TAD), 1973-1976 (Box 38, Folder 316)
    - Special Reports - Technical Assistance Division (TAD) - Ford Foundation-Population Council Meeting, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 317)
    - Special Reports - Technical Assistance Division (TAD) - Matrix for George Zeidenstein, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 318)
    - Special Reports - Technical Assistance Division (TAD) - Program Review, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 319)
    - Special Reports - Hopper Review Committee, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 320)
    - Special Reports - HXH Matrix, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 321)
    - Special Reports - Technical Assistance Division (TAD) - Woods Hole, 1975-1976 (Box 38, Folder 322)